Welcome back to the channel guys,
Ram Ram to all my brothers and today's video is
starting again with Galaxy Toyota
and
according to me there is a minor injury inside the car but there is a full
possibility of part replacement inside that minor injury,
I will show you the entire video and
explain the entire process, I will request you to
watch the video till the end because the video will be
informative for you guys, whatever my
brothers are trying to take insurance claim etc., that is,
how it is taken,
how it is taken, I will make a full video on that,
rest I will also show you the parts etc.,
how much strength it has and whether it is
repaired or not, so
you can see that there is some
impact inside the car and this door is
broken from here, you can see this, we will
try to get it repaired because nothing like that has happened
in it, the rest are minor
scratches,
so to get
it repaired, my MG Toyota is
absolutely clean, so to get it repaired, I will get it done on me, let's
see if the panel is changed or
else this is it  Let's repair the rest of the
insurance policy, so ours has been approved. You
can see that this door has been
removed and now
another door is going to come in its place
and the door has been lifted and placed. This is a
damaged door which the repair company has
not done. The reason was that
this band has been damaged from here, this line will
not be able to be made exactly, that is why the door is being changed. We are
installing the door in it. Let me show
you how the door fits and
how the fittings etc. open. The
rest of it, sir, some things are
not available in the insurance. This
building below the door, this sticker etc., everything is
new. This means I did
not have to use anything old. We are
installing it here and this
door has been installed, the moldings etc. will all
fit in it and as it fits, I will
show you
[Music]
which has been replaced and it has been removed.
Also, its new panel has been
installed here and
its fitting is on, the rest of its fitting from inside is complete.  It is
done, you
can see that all its trim
etc. has been installed
and there is no difference in the rest of the color matching as well
but only its dubbing, polishing etc. is being done, they get it done
and then I will
show you that right now the panel etc. has been replaced
and Toyota's service is very good,
everyone knows that, the
rest of the part is
not available now and I do
not want to go to the after market, so I will remove it, once it is
removed here, then this car will become the same, so
this was some update that has been
changed and if I
show it in detail, which even I will not be able to
show with the camera, but the matching of the pulses etc. is
zero, there is no difference in it, the
rest of the car is still clean, some washes are done,
so I will show you something and
tell you how much bill was made for it in the insurance
and this panel has been painted, there is no difference at all in the paint in the panel,
absolutely
00, they matched it and gave it after dubbing, so
no difference is visible in the
paint  The quality is very good
and now the car has been cleaned a lot
and the cars have come for washing, the
car runs a bit here, then I will show you its final output,
this is being washed, that
means the car has gone for washing, very good, it is a
good service also friend, but
a lot of time is wasted and this car is in washing, the
car is getting ready for delivery.